<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[TheDodds]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[TheDodds]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/thedodds/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 21:15:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/thedodds/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ashman & Katie's Post Wedding]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ashman & Katie's Post Wedding</h1><p>Welcome to Ashman Dodd and Katie Dodd's wedding page! Announcement that Katelynn Weber of Keyser, WV and Ashman Dodd or Romney, WV are getting married on October 4 2014.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b2d6b8b22cd079edd6f5cc6f81ed67d6614b96da.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://doddwedding.info/index-post.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">60b3f6d0-2cbd-42e9-a3ff-bccaa5a99fb9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 21:14:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ashman & Katie's Wedding]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ashman & Katie's Wedding</h1><p>Ashman and Katie met through mutual friends in Morgantown fall of 2008.  Unbeknownst to them, they had both been attending Potomac State College.  Ashman asked for Katie’s number and Katie soon had to trade in her tracfone for a cell phone plan to accommodate their late-night talks and daily conversations.  Katie and Ashman love to spend their time cooking, taking walks, or just talking… as long as it’s together!  Ashman proposed on June 9th, 2013 in front of Cinderella’s Castle at Magic Kingdom in Walt Disney World with a photographer to capture the magical moment.  Ashman and Katie are excitedly taking on the new set of challenges and adventures they face as a couple and, despite the contempt between Ashman and Lucy, Katie’s cat, they are enthusiastic about building their new life together.  The next chapter in their “Happily Ever After” begins on October 4th, 2014, when bride and groom say “I do”.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/30b075fa628522cf7c94b4fcf772fdf6b8fdb80d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://doddwedding.info/index-pre.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ae9aac49-9df9-4987-962e-513189bb9970</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 21:15:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>